<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-28T17:31:22+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">SYCL Safety - SYCL for Safety Practitioners</title><subtitle>Safe SYCL - SYCL for Safety Practitioners. Techical series of blogs or articles for practitioners looking to use SYCL accelerated applications on embedded heterogeneous platforms for safety systems for example, for automotive.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Part 3 SYCL for Safety Practitioners – SYCL ADAS Applications Topology Explained</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/11/09/SYCL-for-Safety-Practitioners-SYCL-ADAS-Applications-Topology-Explained.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 3 SYCL for Safety Practitioners – SYCL ADAS Applications Topology Explained" /><published>2020-11-09T10:17:53+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-09T10:17:53+00:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/11/09/SYCL%20for%20Safety%20Practitioners%20%E2%80%93%20SYCL%20ADAS%20Applications%20Topology%20Explained</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/11/09/SYCL-for-Safety-Practitioners-SYCL-ADAS-Applications-Topology-Explained.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the third article in this series. In the first, I introduced this series of articles for Safety Practitioners assessing the SYCL™ Open Standard programming model. In the previous article, I talked about how SYCL can support many of the demands outlined in chapter 6 of the ISO 26262:2018 functional safety standard. In this article, I will show you how the SYCL stack topology can support functional safety. What do I mean by topology? Topology here means a large-scale structure with many clear distinct layers separated by API boundaries. In each layer there are further structures where data flows between components as well as up and down through the layers in the stack. The shape of the structure is mainly vertical with the application at the top. This article will show how this structure is well defined yet versatile to meet the needs of the automotive application and the demands of the safety practitioner.&lt;br /&gt;
Read more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codeplay.com/portal/blogs/2020/11/09/sycl-safety-part-3.html&quot;&gt;Part 3 - SYCL ADAS Applications Topology Explained&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="SYCL" /><category term="Safety" /><summary type="html">Welcome to the third article in this series. In the first, I introduced this series of articles for Safety Practitioners assessing the SYCL™ Open Standard programming model. In the previous article, I talked about how SYCL can support many of the demands outlined in chapter 6 of the ISO 26262:2018 functional safety standard. In this article, I will show you how the SYCL stack topology can support functional safety. What do I mean by topology? Topology here means a large-scale structure with many clear distinct layers separated by API boundaries. In each layer there are further structures where data flows between components as well as up and down through the layers in the stack. The shape of the structure is mainly vertical with the application at the top. This article will show how this structure is well defined yet versatile to meet the needs of the automotive application and the demands of the safety practitioner. Read more Part 3 - SYCL ADAS Applications Topology Explained.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 2 SYCL for Safety Practitioners – SYCL for Automotive AI and ADAS applications</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/09/01/SYCL-for-Safety-Practitioners-SYCL-for-Automotive-AI-and-ADAS-applications.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 2 SYCL for Safety Practitioners – SYCL for Automotive AI and ADAS applications" /><published>2020-09-01T11:17:53+01:00</published><updated>2020-09-01T11:17:53+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/09/01/SYCL%20for%20Safety%20Practitioners%20%E2%80%93%20SYCL%20for%20Automotive%20AI%20and%20ADAS%20applications</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/09/01/SYCL-for-Safety-Practitioners-SYCL-for-Automotive-AI-and-ADAS-applications.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the second in my series of technical articles. In the last blog, I introduced this series of technical articles for SYCL™ safety practitioners outlining the benefits for you. In this article, I am going to give you an overview of a typical SYCL application for safety applications. This should give you a good platform upon which you can see the anatomy of the ADAS or AI compute stack unfold. This article is an introduction to SYCL much like other SYCL articles or texts but with the focus on safety.&lt;br /&gt;
Read more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.codeplay.com/portal/blogs/2020/09/01/sycl-safety-part-2.html&quot;&gt;Part 2 - SYCL for Automotive AI and ADAS applications&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="SYCL" /><category term="Safety" /><summary type="html">Welcome to the second in my series of technical articles. In the last blog, I introduced this series of technical articles for SYCL™ safety practitioners outlining the benefits for you. In this article, I am going to give you an overview of a typical SYCL application for safety applications. This should give you a good platform upon which you can see the anatomy of the ADAS or AI compute stack unfold. This article is an introduction to SYCL much like other SYCL articles or texts but with the focus on safety. Read more Part 2 - SYCL for Automotive AI and ADAS applications.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Part 1 SYCL for Safety Practitioners – An Introduction</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/07/13/SYCL-for-Safety-Practitioners-An-Introduction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Part 1 SYCL for Safety Practitioners – An Introduction" /><published>2020-07-13T11:17:53+01:00</published><updated>2020-07-13T11:17:53+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/07/13/SYCL%20for%20Safety%20Practitioners%20%E2%80%93%20An%20Introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sycl/safety/2020/07/13/SYCL-for-Safety-Practitioners-An-Introduction.html">&lt;p&gt;First in a series of technical blogs &lt;a href=&quot;https://codeplay.com/portal/blogs/2020/07/13/sycl-safety-part-1.html&quot;&gt;Part 1 - An Introduction&lt;/a&gt;. This blog introduces the SYCL technical articals providing information that practitioners may find useful when looking at the SYCL accelerated stack supporting automotive ADAS systems.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="SYCL" /><category term="Safety" /><summary type="html">First in a series of technical blogs Part 1 - An Introduction. This blog introduces the SYCL technical articals providing information that practitioners may find useful when looking at the SYCL accelerated stack supporting automotive ADAS systems.</summary></entry></feed>